couponwinner.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy – How does CouponWinner.com collect data and secure your information.

## Your Privacy is Our Commitment

CouponWinner.com has created this statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. This privacy policy will outline how CouponWinner.com uses and protects any information you disclose when using our website.

This privacy policy expresses our commitment to the highest level of integrity when using any information you provide to our website.

We are dedicated to ensuring that your personal information stays protected. Should you choose to provide certain information with us, we assure you it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

This policy is subject to change over time. You should check this page regularly to ensure you are aware of changes that have gone into effect. This privacy policy is effective from 13 September 2013.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please contact [Support@CouponWinner.com](mailto:Support@CouponWinner.com) or by mail at:

SurfMyAds.com, Inc.  
321 Santa Monica Blvd, Suite #300  
Santa Monica, CA 90401 USA  
(424) 214-5470

## How Do We Collect Information?

CouponWinner.com collects the personal information you provide when you opt to receive our e-mail newsletter, follow us on social media, share coupons, or enter a promotional giveaway. This information may include your name, e-mail address, or other disclosures that can be used to identify you or any third party member of whom you share information.

  * **Email Newsletter –** Our site is completely free to use without submitting personal information. However, you will be required to submit your e-mail address if you would like to receive our email newsletter. An auto-generated e-mail will then be sent to your inbox asking to confirm your subscription. The information submitted therein will not be shared with any third party, including affiliates, partners, parent companies or subsidiaries for marketing purposes. You may cease to receive e-mail newsletters by clicking the unsubscribe link located in the e-mail newsletter.

  * **Share Coupon –** Users can send coupons to others by using the “Share Coupon” function underneath the brand logo on the coupon. Users will be asked to offer their name and the e-mail address(es) of those they wish to send the coupons to. A one-time e-mail will be sent to the recipient, and he/she will never receive any other coupon, notification or general information in the future.

  * **Social Media Networking –** We use Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, Pinterest, and YouTube to further connect with our users. You may adjust the privacy settings on your social media platform or application and/or manage our interactivity or permissions through your own social media account to manage the information you share with us. We routinely host giveaways via social media and by purpose of entry, you may be asked to provide your name. This is solely for the purpose of participation.

  * **Cookies –** We utilize technology commonly referred to as “cookies” to collect information about how our website is being used. We use cookies to identify which pages are being visited and how often. This helps us analyze information regarding traffic so that we can improve our site by tailoring it to our users’ needs. Essentially, we use cookies to create a better website; they enable us to determine which pages are useful and which are not. Cookies do not provide us with any personal information about you, nor do they give us access to any information on your computer. Please keep in mind that recent versions of browsers give you the capability to reject or accept all, or certain, cookies.

## Website Redirects

Our website contains links to other websites. These links most often direct to merchant websites. It is important to note that we do not have any control over these websites. When you are redirected to another site you are then subject to their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy and protection of any information you wish you extend to such websites. It is prudent to overview the privacy policy of the website in question before surrendering any personal information.

## Controlling Your Personal Information

You may choose to control, restrict or erase entirely the personal information you’ve disclosed by e-mailing us directly at [Support@CouponWinner.com](mailto:Support@CouponWinner.com).

We only intend to utilize your personal information to relay promotional information about third parties to enhance your experience. We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any third parties unless authorized by the law to do so or unless we have obtained your permission.

## Security

Above anything else, we value the loyalty of our users. Under no circumstances would we compromise the safety and privacy of our visitors and customers. We are entirely committed to ensuring your personal information stays secure and protected. We have engineered reliable electronic, physical and managerial procedures to safeguard such information to prevent unauthorized disclosure or access.

CouponWinner.com reserves the right to amend or remove this privacy policy at our discretion.

321 Santa Monica Blvd, Suite #300  
Santa Monica, CA 90401 USA  
**Phone:** 424.214.5470 | **Fax:** 424.214.5488
